Stand up tall, reach out your hand.
Cut through the wind and make a stand.
The paint within brings
out a map of your own.
To the left and the right,
all we saw stormy nights.
All the rough winds and
waves coming day after day.
And the values we had
were about to collapse.
Oh, just where do we go next?
And as we look down to the compass in
hand Is it showing us the right direction?
All we know is nobody
here knows it for certain.
So close your eyes and breathe in deeply.
And listen to your soul.
You'll see a path in front of you.
And you'll know just where you need to go.
So stand up tall, reach out your hand.
Cut through the wind and make us stand.
Don't let the darkness
win, just break through.
I'll do it my own way,
that's what's best for me.
And you do it your way,
that's how it's got to be.
We're moving forward, now I'm ready.
But at times it's okay
to get help on the way.
For the future ahead, burning bright.
For what's ahead you see.
Is beyond your wildest dreams.
So stand up tall, reach out your hand.
Cut through the wind and make a stand.
Don't let the darkness
win, just break through.
We'll do it our way the best that we know.
With tears and doubts and tone.
We'll go where we all wanna go.
The hate within brings colors of our own.
Young Master!
What are you doing down here?
The armory is in the lowest
level of the basement.
I have to hurry!
Please, Momonosuke.
If you can slow the island down even a
little bit, it might make all the difference.
Just keep at it!
No one said this was going to be easy.
Show some persistence, Momonosuke!
Show some guts!
This battle is far from over!
You don't know the limit of your power.
Just keep creating flame clouds.
If Cloud can do it, then you can do it!
And do it better!
More, more!
No harm will come to the Flower
Capital, not under my watch!
I know you wouldn't challenge
an Emperor unprepared.
What have you caught?
Your trump card.
Have you managed to awaken your power?
Because that would be a damn good start.
I'm still working on it.
Right now it takes up a lot of my stamina,
so I need to save it
till I'm on my last leg.
I used it too early.
We'll lose this fight.
Yeah, same thing with me.
But we're not making
any headway like this.
Go all in.
Just follow my lead.
What kind of fool do
you take me for, Kaido?
You think I forgot about
the armory you've been tolt?
I know everything you're
hiding down there!
All those weapons I manufactured,
all those explosives!
This is going to be the biggest
bang in the history of the world!
This is our final scene!
Druid Kanjuro!
Burn it all to the ground!
Drive them into the debris!
Down to our brain!
The souls of the crew?
So we will be joining!
seven in this day's game!
I'm done with you all!
It's time to die!
I won't suffer your
idiocy a moment longer!
Fukurokuju!
Get back here already!
Flower shunikens!
Pathetic earlobe-crackers!
Avenging one's ward is
never pathetic! In need!
Such sentimental nonsense
will be the death of you!
It's time for us to make our exit!
Only Kashima will be blown to pieces,
and the pirates, along with it,
lead them to their meaningless squabble.
Let them all burn!
You little delinquents
have been very naughty,
so take your putter and don't talk back.
Koby!
Ma, ma, ma, ma, ma.
Ha, ha, ha.
Ma, ma, ma, ma.
Looks like I got the noisy one at least.
Too bad, kids.
These two have been holding
off Big Mom all this time?
They must be incredibly strong!
And now I'm gonna take your head!
My, my, my, my!
Go all in!
Just follow my lead!
Cave room.
Anesthesia, ready.
Better brace yourselves, because
this one's going to be painful.
Right back at you.
I'm about to show you
what real pain feels like.
K-Room's incision is
harmless but then it's
true power comes from the
shockwave it generates.
Shock Villa! Ugh!
No!
Are you bleeding?
You cocky little shit!
Get over here right now!
Be careful what you wish for!
Un-dyed!
Why am I sticking to your head, Mama?
You shouldn't turn a lady into a magnet.
Since when do you know such a nasty trick?
This is nasty.
Well, I haven't even gotten
to the good point yet.
What's happening to the steel beams?
The villains are gonna come down!
Huh?
Oh, no!
All right, Trapanga, release it now!
Fine, but don't tell me what to do.
Oh, class!
Let's rock!
Did they win?
They buried her.
Holy shit, she's gotta be dead.
I doubt anyone could survive that.
There you have it.
That's my best trick.
Eat metal, witch.
That's payback for what
you put me through.
So your awakened power magnetizes things.
Big Mom included.
That was nice work, but
how long does it last for?
Just because we worked together once doesn't
mean you get to learn all my secrets.
He's back up already!
Time to choose.
Life or Oshiruko!
This is bad!
She's using Soul Pucci on us!
So wait, what do we do?
We've got the soup she wants, don't we?
Uh, no, we kind of smelled it all earlier.
If we don't give her soup,
she'll steal our life force away!
No!
Get out, you fools!
It's time to end this.
I'll give you life!
I'll even throw in a year's
worth of my own lifespan!
It's my fury given form.
The only way to make
myself even more powerful?
She's growing too.
I mean, on the bright side,
she's a much bigger target now.
What a disaster.
I can't cut through that.
I can't send her flying either.
She's too damn big.
She was huge already it's too much how do
you even fight this and
the fire's closing in?
This has gotten completely
out of hand you're
right this floor is a
living nightmare like hell
itself you've really out done yourselves
it's been a long time
since I felt pain like
this decades in fact if
nothing else I respect
your strength Trafalgar Law Captain Kidd
You're just like Straw Hat luffy
aren't you you young upstarts
all think you can push me aside
but I won't be replaced so easily
You know some of us are just
trying to study history?
I shouldn't have to fight monsters
just to learn a thing or two.
Quit your damn complaining.
As long as we live, we have to fight.
I'll knock her on that
throne even if it kills me.
You want to be an emperor that badly?
Fine, but you'll have to wrest
the title from my cold, dead body.
I'm sure there are lots of guards ahead.
I'll head to the cave
chamber and take a side path.
Are you nuts?
What the hell do you think you're doing?
Are you trying to make even more enemies?
We were never allies.
Fine, then screw you!
Scratch!
Huh sorry Apu but the game is over.
I know how your attacks work now
I'm calling your bluff there pal at
first I thought they Didn't have a
vector but then I watched closely and
I figured it out they fire when your
target Hears you and you aim them
with your sight hey you keep your
mouth shut those are trade secrets.
All right, whatever, you got me.
But you're still screwed, Dino Boy! Look!
There's no way you're taking
down three numbers on your own!
I'm not backing down.
I have an obligation to
Straw Hat and his crew.
My honor demands that I
beat you here and now.
Oh, hey, Drake and Apu.
Uh, what are you doing in the back rooms?
You partying?
Right back at you, young master!
Why are you busting down walls?
Bringing down the house is my job!
I thought you were on
the roof fighting Kaido.
What happened?
I need to get to the armory right now.
What's going on here?
Yamato doesn't know he's
a traitor yet, right?
Whatever.
Drake is useless to me either way.
Okay, new plan.
Drake, I need to get past you.
Yo, hold up, hold up.
One sec, young master.
I got good news.
Come on, just trust me.
Sorry, but it'll have to wait.
I'm in a big hurry right now.
And besides that, you and I
aren't on the same team anymore.
I finally cut all ties with Kaido. I dig.
That's even better, actually.
I told you I'm in a hurry.
I don't have time to play games with you.
And I don't have time to fight
one of the Toby Rope either.
So you'd better get out of
my way! Wait, Yamato! Enough!
I'll run straight through you!
You've been warned!
Please, just wait!
I've waited long enough already! Now move!
You don't want to pick
a fight with me, Drake!
Of course I don't!
We're on the same side!
I cut ties with the Beast
Pirates just like you!
Really?
Well, that's handy.
Then I hope you don't hold
it against me when I do this!
All right, time to get out of here.
I have to save Onigashima and
the flower capital! Sweet!
Why is everyone so stupid?
Good help really is hard to find.
If I can get Yamato on my side, I'm good.
Hey!
Where are you running off to?
Is someone after me?
Fuga!
Huh?
Hey, Fuga!
I gotta go!
Wait a sec!
Fuga!
What?!
Just don't leave!
I need you, man! Come back!
Why is everybody screwing me over?
Hey!
This is no time to be
drinking, you two! Follow me!
We gotta stop them!
Come on, Yamato!
You're my dick and out of this mess!
Get back here, I'm poop!
Run away, Baron Corp.
And leave you? Yes.
We'll stay here and fight.
You gotta keep Nico Robin safe.
All right, we'll go, but
be careful. We'll be fine.
We're not so helpless.
Come on, Robin.
You heard what they said, right?
They'll be killed.
That's precisely why we must go.
We cannot allow their
sacrifice to be in vain.
I can't believe they're defeating
the Mink Warriors so easily.
Whoever those men are,
they're terribly strong.
CP0.
They're a Cipher pole unit.
We saw them before, back in Dressrosa.
They're government officers, right?
Intelligence agents?
But what are they doing here?
And why are they looking
for you at a time like this?
I couldn't say, but we're
facing the worst case scenario.
That much is apparent at least. What?
Cape is the top-ranked
unit in all of Cypher-Pole.
And the masked agents are the
most dangerous, even amongst them.
It seems that our escape
options are a little bare-bound.
Yo-ho-ho!
Well, look at you.
Now, come on.
Let's get you to somewhere safe.
Time to fly!
Where are you?
Jaggy!
This is a disaster...
Um, excuse me?
Could you help me?
Whoever you are?
Judge used to talk about this.
Please, I have nothing to do with this!
I'm just a geisha from the Capitol!
He wanted to create the perfect soldier.
Shut up!
With incredible strength
and a heart of ice.
Powerful and merciless. Shut up!
I just want to go home!
Can you help me get out of here?
Don't pretend you're not excited to show
off that germ of blood in your veins!
I'm not like them, dammit!
I'M HUMAN!
What?
Are you okay, miss? Stay back!
Don't come any closer!
I need help!
Osume, what happened?
You're bleeding!
I did this to you!
Miss, are you alright?
Let me help you.
How dare you attack this poor girl!
You call yourself a man!
Please, you've got this wrong.
I would never... Excuses!
You're fighting on the
side of Wano, aren't you?
Of course I am.
Then you're doing this to your own people.
Listen to me.
I don't know what happened to her.
I just showed up and...
I didn't...
I didn't do anything.
I didn't lay a finger on her.
I was just.
I don't know.
If you're so innocent, why did she run?
I don't want to hear a word.
It doesn't matter what you say.
We're trying to hide now.
Leave before someone finds this place.
Monsters who beat up innocent
girls are not welcome here.
I swear this wasn't me.
I promised you. Shut up.
Get out of here.
Go!
Haven't you done enough?
Don't ever show your face here again!
Stop it!
Go on, leave!
Please, I wouldn't...
I couldn't...
This isn't happening.
I would never lay a hand on a lady.
Hey, Jermaboy!
Found you!
What you doing over here?
Hate to break it to you, but
the pleasure hall's closed.
No way.
That's the last thing I would do.
I could never hurt a woman.
Could I?
They feed a woman unconscious.
Everything you guys represent
goes against my principles.
You're telling me I'm
going to end up like them?
Yeah.
My body isn't tingling anymore.
Maybe it already happened.
I was caught up in my thoughts when
I ran into that girl in the hallway.
It took me a second to notice her, and
then she went flying, and she was bleeding.
She looked at me with fear in her eyes.
Dammit.
Hey, Luffy.
What kind of man do you want on your crew?
An unreliable dreamer like me,
who's afraid of his own power,
who's helpless every
time he faces a woman?
Or a warrior of science who can beat up a
monster like this
without a second thought,
who has a heart of ice and a
will of steel that never fails?
Which would be more useful
to the King of the Pirates?
I need you on my crew, Saadji!
Without you!
I don't know what'll happen
from here on out, but...
Is that the Germa suit?
Are you gonna wear it?
I know what I have to do.
When I put this suit on,
it awakened a power that's been
inside me since I was born.
I can't do anything to change that.
Sounds like you finally get it.
Now, suit up, Jermaboy!
What I can do is put
an end to all of this.
I need you on my crew, Sanji!
Without you, without you, I'll
never be king of the pirates!
It's over.
I'm choosing my own fate.
What the hell are you doing?
I said put it on.
Not destroy it.
Goodbye, Jeremiah.
Goodbye, women's back.
I'm gonna finish this
fight on my own terms.
Huh?
Collect.
What the hell?
When do I have this thing?
Who's calling me at a time like this?
I'm busy!
I was afraid you might be
dying in a ditch somewhere.
So I snuck that snail on
you as a safety precaution.
I'm not dying, you idiot!
Could you leave me alone?
Listen, this won't take long.
I know we got this.
We're beating the beast
pirates no matter what.
Yeah, of course we are!
But after the battle, there's a chance
I might not be in my right mind anymore.
If that happens, then kill me. What?
He's still there?
Yeah, I got it.
No problem.
I'll kill you, just like you asked.
I don't get what your problem is, but at
least I got something to look forward to.
So until then, don't you dare die on me.
I appreciate it.
lick.
Hey, where'd you go?
You got invisibility tech?
Bet daddy gave you that too, huh?
I don't need you adding fuel to the fire.
Because I'm already burning up!
I'M SENDING YOU STRAIGHT TO HELL!
HELL MEMORIES!